That's it.
All the aesthetic programs are college preparatory.
Most aesthetic schools also offer the courses you need for special permits.
It can be important for the students to bring with you if you want to be specifically late.
Are these knowledge really applicable in reality?
What do I become if I am good at keeping up with 3D models or maybe game graphics.
Should you niche so narrow already when you are so young?
Then I usually say that these knowledge is applicable even after school.
I have companies that contact me and ask "Can't your students come to us and make 3D models?"
Because it is an important knowledge to have also against other industries other than just the gaming industry.
It can be architectural firms.
Tech companies that are doing AR and that want you to be able to do such things simply.
It is something that you might just plug in for a test.
Then you forget it.
It does not feel like we will use it in the future.
It is better to focus on what has to do with the profession.
Maybe sometime in a quiz so you can get a question from the lessons.
It's fun to go to high school.
Nice that everyone agrees here.
What do you think Elin.
Why is it fun to go to high school.
It depends a lot on which school you choose.
So it is fun to take interest over something you want to take interest over.
When elementary school in very wide
over subjects and so on and trying to teach an everything,
So you really have to focus on something in high school.
It can be very engaging and it becomes much more fun to learn some stuff.
I agree with it was great fun to go to high school.
Thousand thanks!
Well done all.
Thanks!
Big thanks to today's participants.
As you can see, it is best to start from what you want to get a good and fun high school time.
To be able to compare different programs or schools is to visit an open house a good tip.
Under prevailing circumstances, several schools offer a digital version instead.